Bruno de A. Bisogni

PRODUCT MANAGER



Objectives

Project Manager, PO and Scrum MAster



PRICES

Second Place

E-sus

E-SUS Project: Heat Map that indicates the percentage of medicine stocks at SUS posts

https://github.com/brunobisogniDesenvolvedor/hacksus

- 2017

First Place

Second IMA Hackthon Campinas

Agenda Sus

Primeiro Lugar

Secretária de Transportes de São Paulo

Like a Bus

Development of an app that, through image recognition, informed in real time the capacity of buses in the city of são paulo.

All the Awards, which are 17 in total, have en described on Likedin, I worked with the m as PM and PO for building solutions and

LANGUAGE

ENGLISH

SPANISH

ITALIAN



PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES

2022 - 2023

W/Time

São Paulo/SF

june- Jan

Analista de costumer insight senior - BPO

powerBi, Google bigquery, Criando prototipos e Analise de KPIS

2019-2020

Levoo - Same Day Delivery

São Paulo/SP

São Paulo/SP

Sales & Marketing · Technical Leadership · SEO Writing · Project Management · Google Analytics · Search Engine Optimization (SEO) · Digital Marketing Data Analysis · Scrum · Search Marketing (SEM), Development team leadership, use of agile methodology, Node js, C#, Ruby-Rails, Reac and Reac Native, AWS Cloud, GCP, big query, SQL Server,

Query Creation

2017-2018

VIRTUAL LIGHT

Set-Mar

CFO - PM

Sales & Marketing \cdot Technical Leadership \cdot SEO Writing \cdot Project Management \cdot Google Analytics \cdot Search Engine Optimization (SEO) \cdot Digital Marketing Data Analysis \cdot Scrum \cdot Search Marketing (SEM),Development team leadership, use of agile methodology,Node js,C#,Ruby-Rails,Reac and Reac Native,AWS Cloud,GCP,big query,SQL Server,

Query Creation, Unity, VR with Oculus Rift, VR creation Envoirment

2019-2020

ABCE Service Jul-Set

СТО-СМО-РМ

Sales & Marketing \cdot Technical Leadership \cdot SEO Writing \cdot Project Management \cdot Google Analytics \cdot Search Engine Optimization (SEO) \cdot Digital Marketing Data Analysis \cdot Scrum \cdot Search Marketing (SEM), Development team leadership, use of agile methodology, Cloud, GCP, big query, SQL Server, Data Analyse, metrics and KPIs, Okrs



SKILLS

DESIGN

PHOTOSHOP

ILLUSTRATOR INDESIGN

MS-OFFICE

FIGMA

MIRO

CERTIFICATIOS

GERENTE DE ECOMMERCE E MARKETING DIGITAL COMSCHOOL

CURSO AVANÇADO DE GOOGLE ANALYTICS, DATA STUDIO E TAG MANAGER

ESPECIALISTA EM GOOGLE MARKETING AVANÇADO COMSCHOOL

> REDAÇÃO DE SEO COMSCHOOL

HUSTER INSIDE SALES, TÉCNICAS DE VENDAS **GAME ACADEMY**

> FORMAÇÃO EM DESIGN GRÁFICO **RED ZERO SCHOOL**

PROGRAMA AVANÇADO DE GESTÃO DE ECOMMERCE COMSCHOOL

> SCRUM ESSENCIAL MIDMASTER TREINAMENTOS



ACADEMIC EDUCATION

2021

Universidade Anhembi-morumbi

Bacharel em Design de Games

See on linkedin de complete resume just Scanner





I'M WAITING TO YOU CALL TO TALK